Guide to the Yale Club of Washington, D.C., Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Club of Washington, D.C., records
1874-1982
RU 532
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
5.5
(3 boxes)
The records consist of articles of association, constitution, amendments, and minutes of meetings documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Club of Washington, D.C.
Yale Club of Washington (D.C.)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 8-C-2 (YRG 8-C-2), Records of Yale regional alumni organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of articles of association, constitution, amendments, and minutes of meetings documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Club of Washington, D.C.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale Club of Washington (D.C.); Yale University -- Alumnae and alumnae -- Societies, etc.
- Records, 1949-1962; Accession 1962-A-002
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically by year only.
  Scope and Contents
  Folders contents may include correspondence; meeting minutes; newspaper clippings; programs and agendas; reports; and Constitution and By-Laws. Contents of folders may vary.
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Records, 1874-1952, 1979-1982; Accession 1982-A-064
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018.
  - Article of Association, Amendments, Minutes of Meetings, 1874-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors - Members of the Corporation, Schedule of Director' Luncheons, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of Directors' Meetings, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 5)
- Records, 1972-1980; Accession 1985-A-075
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2016.
  Photographs are in the Yale Picture Collection YRG 48
  - Minutes: Meetings of Board of Directors
    - 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constitution and By-Laws (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Return of Organization Exempt from Income Tax form, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)